You wake up
You wake up in
You wake up in Thomas
wake up in Thomas Farriner's
up in Thomas Farriner's bakery.
in Thomas Farriner's bakery. The
Thomas Farriner's bakery. The bread
Farriner's bakery. The bread ovens
bakery. The bread ovens glow
The bread ovens glow with
bread ovens glow with banked
ovens glow with banked coals.
glow with banked coals. It's
with banked coals. It's two
banked coals. It's two in
coals. It's two in the
It's two in the morning,
two in the morning, September
in the morning, September second,
the morning, September second, sixteen
morning, September second, sixteen sixty-six.
September second, sixteen sixty-six.
second, sixteen sixty-six.