The bridge itself
The bridge itself catches
The bridge itself catches fire.
bridge itself catches fire. Massive
itself catches fire. Massive timber
catches fire. Massive timber beams
fire. Massive timber beams glow
Massive timber beams glow red-hot.
timber beams glow red-hot. You
beams glow red-hot. You slide
glow red-hot. You slide toward
red-hot. You slide toward the
You slide toward the Thames
slide toward the Thames forty
toward the Thames forty feet
the Thames forty feet below,
Thames forty feet below, still
forty feet below, still reaching
feet below, still reaching for
below, still reaching for help
still reaching for help that
reaching for help that never
for help that never comes.
help that never comes.
that never comes.