But the bridge
But the bridge gatehouse
But the bridge gatehouse becomes
the bridge gatehouse becomes a
bridge gatehouse becomes a trap.
gatehouse becomes a trap. The
becomes a trap. The portcullis
a trap. The portcullis jammed
trap. The portcullis jammed shut
The portcullis jammed shut decades
portcullis jammed shut decades ago.
jammed shut decades ago. Medieval
shut decades ago. Medieval crowd
decades ago. Medieval crowd control
ago. Medieval crowd control fails
Medieval crowd control fails completely.
crowd control fails completely. You
control fails completely. You realize
fails completely. You realize safety
completely. You realize safety is
You realize safety is always
realize safety is always an
safety is always an illusion.
is always an illusion.
always an illusion.