You stumble into
You stumble into Pudding
You stumble into Pudding Lane
stumble into Pudding Lane as
into Pudding Lane as timber
Pudding Lane as timber buildings
Lane as timber buildings catch
as timber buildings catch fire.
timber buildings catch fire. Neighbors
buildings catch fire. Neighbors flee
catch fire. Neighbors flee in
fire. Neighbors flee in their
Neighbors flee in their nightshirts.
flee in their nightshirts. London
in their nightshirts. London hasn't
their nightshirts. London hasn't seen
nightshirts. London hasn't seen rain
London hasn't seen rain in
hasn't seen rain in months.
seen rain in months.
rain in months.