You join thousands
You join thousands fleeing
You join thousands fleeing toward
join thousands fleeing toward London
thousands fleeing toward London Bridge.
fleeing toward London Bridge. The
toward London Bridge. The medieval
London Bridge. The medieval city
Bridge. The medieval city burns
The medieval city burns behind
medieval city burns behind you
city burns behind you in
burns behind you in a
behind you in a crescent
you in a crescent of
in a crescent of orange
a crescent of orange fire.
crescent of orange fire. Surely
of orange fire. Surely stone
orange fire. Surely stone is
fire. Surely stone is safer
Surely stone is safer than
stone is safer than wood.
is safer than wood.
safer than wood.