Four days later,
Four days later, they
Four days later, they find
days later, they find you
later, they find you in
they find you in the
find you in the Thames
you in the Thames mud.
in the Thames mud. Exactly
the Thames mud. Exactly where
Thames mud. Exactly where you
mud. Exactly where you fell.
Exactly where you fell. Still
where you fell. Still reaching
you fell. Still reaching upward.
fell. Still reaching upward. The
Still reaching upward. The Great
reaching upward. The Great Fire
upward. The Great Fire consumed
The Great Fire consumed eighty-seven
Great Fire consumed eighty-seven churches
Fire consumed eighty-seven churches and
consumed eighty-seven churches and thirteen
eighty-seven churches and thirteen thousand
churches and thirteen thousand homes.
and thirteen thousand homes. But
thirteen thousand homes. But it
thousand homes. But it preserved
homes. But it preserved you
But it preserved you perfectly.
it preserved you perfectly.
preserved you perfectly.