Three days. The
Three days. The fire
Three days. The fire burns
days. The fire burns for
The fire burns for three
fire burns for three days.
burns for three days. Twenty-eight
for three days. Twenty-eight thousand
three days. Twenty-eight thousand buildings.
days. Twenty-eight thousand buildings. Over
Twenty-eight thousand buildings. Over three
thousand buildings. Over three thousand
buildings. Over three thousand souls.
Over three thousand souls. Two
three thousand souls. Two hundred
thousand souls. Two hundred and
souls. Two hundred and twenty-seven
Two hundred and twenty-seven thousand
hundred and twenty-seven thousand people
and twenty-seven thousand people with
twenty-seven thousand people with nothing.
thousand people with nothing. The
people with nothing. The city
with nothing. The city that
nothing. The city that thought
The city that thought it
city that thought it was
that thought it was invincible,
thought it was invincible, leveled
it was invincible, leveled to
was invincible, leveled to ash.
invincible, leveled to ash.
leveled to ash.