You wake in
You wake in darkness.
You wake in darkness. The
wake in darkness. The bed
in darkness. The bed is
darkness. The bed is moving.
The bed is moving. Not
bed is moving. Not rocking
is moving. Not rocking —
moving. Not rocking — bucking.
Not rocking — bucking. The
rocking — bucking. The walls
— bucking. The walls scream.
bucking. The walls scream. San
The walls scream. San Francisco,
walls scream. San Francisco, April
scream. San Francisco, April eighteenth,
San Francisco, April eighteenth, nineteen
Francisco, April eighteenth, nineteen oh
April eighteenth, nineteen oh six.
eighteenth, nineteen oh six. Five
nineteen oh six. Five twelve
oh six. Five twelve AM.
six. Five twelve AM. Forty-seven
Five twelve AM. Forty-seven seconds
twelve AM. Forty-seven seconds that
AM. Forty-seven seconds that erase
Forty-seven seconds that erase everything.
seconds that erase everything.
that erase everything.