The shaking stops.
The shaking stops. The
The shaking stops. The silence
shaking stops. The silence is
stops. The silence is worse.
The silence is worse. South
silence is worse. South of
is worse. South of Market
worse. South of Market is
South of Market is gone.
of Market is gone. Wooden
Market is gone. Wooden buildings,
is gone. Wooden buildings, pancaked.
gone. Wooden buildings, pancaked. And
Wooden buildings, pancaked. And from
buildings, pancaked. And from three
pancaked. And from three directions,
And from three directions, smoke.
from three directions, smoke. The
three directions, smoke. The gas
directions, smoke. The gas mains
smoke. The gas mains are
The gas mains are broken.
gas mains are broken. The
mains are broken. The fires
are broken. The fires have
broken. The fires have already
The fires have already started.
fires have already started.
have already started.