And there you
And there you sit.
And there you sit. In
there you sit. In the
you sit. In the centre
sit. In the centre of
In the centre of absence.
the centre of absence. They
centre of absence. They will
of absence. They will rebuild,
absence. They will rebuild, of
They will rebuild, of course.
will rebuild, of course. They
rebuild, of course. They always
of course. They always do.
course. They always do. But
They always do. But in
always do. But in the
do. But in the rubble
But in the rubble beneath
in the rubble beneath Market
the rubble beneath Market Street,
rubble beneath Market Street, they
beneath Market Street, they will
Market Street, they will find
Street, they will find a
they will find a pocket
will find a pocket watch,
find a pocket watch, stopped
a pocket watch, stopped at
pocket watch, stopped at five
watch, stopped at five twelve.
stopped at five twelve. Some
at five twelve. Some moments,
five twelve. Some moments, it
twelve. Some moments, it turns
Some moments, it turns out,
moments, it turns out, last
it turns out, last forever.
turns out, last forever.
out, last forever.