The fire moves
The fire moves faster
The fire moves faster than
fire moves faster than you
moves faster than you can
faster than you can run.
than you can run. Entire
you can run. Entire blocks
can run. Entire blocks ignite
run. Entire blocks ignite at
Entire blocks ignite at once.
blocks ignite at once. The
ignite at once. The heat
at once. The heat is
once. The heat is so
The heat is so intense,
heat is so intense, buildings
is so intense, buildings catch
so intense, buildings catch fire
intense, buildings catch fire from
buildings catch fire from fifty
catch fire from fifty feet
fire from fifty feet away.
from fifty feet away. No
fifty feet away. No water.
feet away. No water. No
away. No water. No plan.
No water. No plan. Just
water. No plan. Just wind
No plan. Just wind and
plan. Just wind and flame.
Just wind and flame.
wind and flame.