The Army tries
The Army tries dynamite.
The Army tries dynamite. They
Army tries dynamite. They blow
tries dynamite. They blow up
dynamite. They blow up buildings
They blow up buildings to
blow up buildings to make
up buildings to make firebreaks.
buildings to make firebreaks. The
to make firebreaks. The embers
make firebreaks. The embers sail
firebreaks. The embers sail right
The embers sail right over.
embers sail right over. Worse
sail right over. Worse —
right over. Worse — the
over. Worse — the blasts
Worse — the blasts spread
— the blasts spread the
the blasts spread the fire
blasts spread the fire further.
spread the fire further. They
the fire further. They are
fire further. They are saving
further. They are saving the
They are saving the city
are saving the city by
saving the city by destroying
the city by destroying it.
city by destroying it.
by destroying it.