You wake up
You wake up on
You wake up on cobblestones.
wake up on cobblestones. The
up on cobblestones. The air
on cobblestones. The air is
cobblestones. The air is thick
The air is thick and
air is thick and sweet.
is thick and sweet. It's
thick and sweet. It's January
and sweet. It's January in
sweet. It's January in Boston,
It's January in Boston, and
January in Boston, and something
in Boston, and something is
Boston, and something is very
and something is very wrong.
something is very wrong. That
is very wrong. That steel
very wrong. That steel tank
wrong. That steel tank above
That steel tank above you
steel tank above you holds
tank above you holds two
above you holds two million
you holds two million gallons.
holds two million gallons. It's
two million gallons. It's been
million gallons. It's been leaking
gallons. It's been leaking for
It's been leaking for years.
been leaking for years.
leaking for years.