You duck into
You duck into an
You duck into an alley.
duck into an alley. The
into an alley. The molasses
an alley. The molasses follows.
alley. The molasses follows. It
The molasses follows. It rises
molasses follows. It rises to
follows. It rises to your
It rises to your waist.
rises to your waist. You
to your waist. You jump
your waist. You jump for
waist. You jump for a
You jump for a fire
jump for a fire escape.
for a fire escape. You
a fire escape. You miss.
fire escape. You miss. Here's
escape. You miss. Here's the
You miss. Here's the thing
miss. Here's the thing about
Here's the thing about molasses
the thing about molasses —
thing about molasses — the
about molasses — the colder
molasses — the colder it
— the colder it gets,
the colder it gets, the
colder it gets, the harder
it gets, the harder it
gets, the harder it holds.
the harder it holds.
harder it holds.