You try to
You try to warn
You try to warn them.
try to warn them. The
to warn them. The longshoremen
warn them. The longshoremen laugh.
them. The longshoremen laugh. The
The longshoremen laugh. The children
longshoremen laugh. The children keep
laugh. The children keep playing.
The children keep playing. A
children keep playing. A grandmother
keep playing. A grandmother walks
playing. A grandmother walks right
A grandmother walks right past
grandmother walks right past you.
walks right past you. Only
right past you. Only the
past you. Only the horse
you. Only the horse understands.
Only the horse understands. It
the horse understands. It pulls
horse understands. It pulls at
understands. It pulls at its
It pulls at its rope,
pulls at its rope, nostrils
at its rope, nostrils flared.
its rope, nostrils flared.
rope, nostrils flared.