Sailors from the
Sailors from the USS
Sailors from the USS Nantucket
from the USS Nantucket wade
the USS Nantucket wade in
USS Nantucket wade in wearing
Nantucket wade in wearing white.
wade in wearing white. They
in wearing white. They leave
wearing white. They leave wearing
white. They leave wearing brown.
They leave wearing brown. One
leave wearing brown. One hundred
wearing brown. One hundred fifty
brown. One hundred fifty people
One hundred fifty people are
hundred fifty people are trapped.
fifty people are trapped. Rescue
people are trapped. Rescue takes
are trapped. Rescue takes four
trapped. Rescue takes four days.
Rescue takes four days. The
takes four days. The smell
four days. The smell will
days. The smell will linger
The smell will linger for
smell will linger for decades.
will linger for decades.
linger for decades.