A wave of
A wave of molasses
A wave of molasses fifteen
wave of molasses fifteen feet
of molasses fifteen feet high
molasses fifteen feet high surges
fifteen feet high surges at
feet high surges at thirty-five
high surges at thirty-five miles
surges at thirty-five miles per
at thirty-five miles per hour.
thirty-five miles per hour. You
miles per hour. You run.
per hour. You run. It's
hour. You run. It's faster.
You run. It's faster. It
run. It's faster. It swallows
It's faster. It swallows the
faster. It swallows the railway,
It swallows the railway, the
swallows the railway, the buildings,
the railway, the buildings, the
railway, the buildings, the street.
the buildings, the street. Twenty-one
buildings, the street. Twenty-one people
the street. Twenty-one people will
street. Twenty-one people will not
Twenty-one people will not go
people will not go home
will not go home tonight.
not go home tonight.
go home tonight.