You lie at
You lie at the
You lie at the flood's
lie at the flood's edge.
at the flood's edge. A
the flood's edge. A doorway,
flood's edge. A doorway, ten
edge. A doorway, ten feet
A doorway, ten feet ahead,
doorway, ten feet ahead, stands
ten feet ahead, stands open.
feet ahead, stands open. Your
ahead, stands open. Your hand
stands open. Your hand reaches
open. Your hand reaches for
Your hand reaches for it.
hand reaches for it. You
reaches for it. You never
for it. You never arrive.
it. You never arrive. For
You never arrive. For thirty
never arrive. For thirty years,
arrive. For thirty years, on
For thirty years, on hot
thirty years, on hot summer
years, on hot summer days,
on hot summer days, the
hot summer days, the North
summer days, the North End
days, the North End smells
the North End smells of
North End smells of molasses.
End smells of molasses. A
smells of molasses. A sweet
of molasses. A sweet ghost.
molasses. A sweet ghost. Just
A sweet ghost. Just like
sweet ghost. Just like you.
ghost. Just like you.
Just like you.