What happens if you warn the Titanic?
Imagine waking up in 1912. Cold air,
endless ocean, and someone whispers,
"You're on the Titanic." And you
remember one thing. "Tonight, 11:40 p.m.
Iceberg." I check my pockets. No phone,
no proof, just panic. I run to warn the
officers. Iceberg, tonight 11:40,
starboard side. It rips open six
compartments. They laugh. Sir, this ship
is unsinkable. That's when I realize
authority won't save anyone. So, I
change the plan. Find the people who
matter.
>> Jack Rose. Jack.
>> Rose. She turns. Last night you climbed
over that railing. Her face goes pale.
Only a few people knew that. I look at
Jack. You talked her down. You said the
water would feel like a thousand knives.
His smile disappears.
>> What I am about to tell you changes
everything.
>> Now they're not looking at me like I'm
crazy. They're looking at me like I
shouldn't exist. Jack starts shouting to
the others. Iceberg tonight 11:40.
People stare. Some laugh. One man says,
"Go back to third class." That's when it
hits me. Pride is louder than fear. So,
we stop trying to save everyone. We
move. We get to a lifeboat early. People
call us crazy. Then the engines stop. A
long metal scrape screams. The ship
tilts. Everything I said happens. Jack
stares at the sinking ship, then at me,
and says, "Who are you?"
>> I look at him. Trust me, I'm the only
one who knows how this ends.