What if you actually switched to an
iPhone after using Samsung for years?
First 8 seconds, I already knew I made a
mistake. It looks clean, calm, innocent,
like it never did anything wrong in its
life. I unlock it, try to go back. There
is no back button. I just freeze. My
thumb is hovering. I swipe left.
Nothing. Swipe right. Something
happened. I don't know what happened.
Swipe up. Now everything disappeared. At
this point, I'm not using the phone. The
phone is using me. Fine. Easy task. Set
an alarm. On Samsung, it tells you
everything. You will sleep 7 hours and
12 minutes. Peace. Emotional support.
Here I set 6:30. Now I'm opening
calculator because apparently I need to
calculate my own suffering. I didn't buy
a phone. I bought math. I just wanted
sleep, not homework. Whatever. Let's
text someone. I type one sentence.
Autocorrect immediately disrespects me.
It changes words, adds words, removes
words. Now I'm rereading my own message
like I never said that. I'm not texting
anymore. I'm negotiating. Samsung
keyboard felt like I got you. This one
feels like, are you sure that's what you
meant? Okay, let's install my favorite
app. Search it. Not there. I check
Chrome. There's no APK. No freedom. If
Apple doesn't approve it, it doesn't
exist. All right. Settings. This should
be easy. On my old phone. Tap. Tap.
Done. Here. I entered settings. And now
I'm scrolling through 47 options that
all sound important. I forgot why I came
here. I leave with nothing. After one
week, I picked up my Samsung again. It
had percentages. It had a back button.
It had respect.