What if you woke up in Jerusalem knowing
Jesus Christ dies today? Hour one. You
wake on cold stone. The air feels heavy,
suffocating. People move quickly past
you, whispering, avoiding eye contact.
You grab a stranger and ask what's
happening. He pulls away and says, "They
took him." Your chest tightens. You
already know who. Hour three. You reach
the courtyard. Roman soldiers stand in
lines, impenetrable. Behind them, a
broken figure stands surrounded by
guards. This isn't the sanitized version
you've seen in paintings. This is
visceral. You push forward, shouting for
them to stop, but a soldier strikes you
down. No one defends you. Hour four. The
crowd shifts. And then you see her Mary.
She isn't screaming. She isn't fighting.
She's just breaking. You want to walk to
her. You want to say something, but your
legs won't move. You realize there is
nothing you could say that wouldn't make
this moment worse. Hour six. They force
the cross onto his back. The wood slams
into torn skin. You follow through the
streets, yelling, begging, telling the
soldiers they're making a mistake, but
no one listens. History moves forward
like a heavy tide and you are drowning
in it. Hour nine. The sky grows darker.
The air turns cold. The crowd becomes
quiet. You feel it in your chest before
you understand it in your mind. This is
the moment, the one moment billions of
people will remember. And you are
standing inside it completely powerless.
Final hour. The crowd leaves. The noise
disappears. You stand there empty. Then
the weight in the air lifts. You came
here believing you could stop it. But
now you understand this moment was never
yours to control. You failed to save
him. But you realize that was the only
way the story could