I switched from iPhone to Samsung and at
first it felt illegal. Bigger screen,
more control, endless customization,
battery lasts forever. I thought I
escaped. I didn't know I was walking
into something else. It all started with
a text. Green bubble shame hit
different. Opened the family group chat
and felt my soul leave my body.
Everyone's blue bubbles laughing at my
green ass. Photos look like 2009 JPEGs.
My friends keep asking, "You good, bro?"
And that was just the beginning. Took a
fire pick at dinner. Instinctively go to
AirDrop it. Phone said, "No devices
found. Now I'm texting Links like my
uncle in 2012." It didn't stop there.
AirPods, just regular headphones now. No
auto switch, no spatial audio. Siri
don't even know me. Our relationship
died the day I switched. Then it got
personal. My Apple Watch in the drawer
giving me side eye. Notifications
halfbroken. We used to be in love. Now
we're just Facebook friends. Every
morning reminded me, having to actually
press my finger to unlock. I feel like
I'm clocking in for a shift. My muscle
memory started fighting me. Kept swiping
up for control center and nothing
happens. Accidentally opened 12 apps
trying to go back. My brain is glitching
hard. And when I thought I'd adapt, took
me 15 minutes to find do not disturb. I
thought I was unlucky cuz I'm black.
Nah, the real racism is when your ex
says, "Why you on Android though? Broke
energy. That one hurt. Now my friends
won't stop roasting me. Why did you
leave the cult? Green bubble gang rise
up. I'm now the funny story at parties."
While telling everyone best decision
ever on my story, I'm privately
googling. How easy is it to switch back
to