What if you never showered again? Day
one, you skip a shower. It's fine.
Nobody notices. Week one. Okay, people
notice. Your mom opens your door and
immediately
>> When was the last time you opened a
window?
>> Not that bad, Mom.
>> Not that bad. It smells like something
that All right.
>> Month one, your room has its own weather
system. You spray perfume. It makes it
worse. Even the flies are thinking
twice. Year 1, your hoodie is basically
your skin now. You take it off and it
stands by itself. Your body has
officially adjusted to natural mode.
Year 10. Your immune system is strong.
Bacteria aren't your enemies anymore.
They're roommates. Year 30. A fly landed
on you and pass out. Scientists would
study you, but they can't get close
enough. Year 60. You end best friends
locked in. Then one day you see a cute
girl. Suddenly, you remember you're
human. And you think, "Bro, today is the
day." You walk into the bathroom. You
turn on the shower. Water hits your
body. Your skin is confused. Your immune
system goes, "What is this attack?" 5
minutes later, you're clean. You're
fresh. You smell amazing. You step
outside. You smile at her.