Three kilometers away,
Three kilometers away, Pripyat.
Three kilometers away, Pripyat. Forty-nine
kilometers away, Pripyat. Forty-nine thousand
away, Pripyat. Forty-nine thousand people.
Pripyat. Forty-nine thousand people. Children
Forty-nine thousand people. Children are
thousand people. Children are playing
people. Children are playing outside.
Children are playing outside. No
are playing outside. No one
playing outside. No one has
outside. No one has been
No one has been told.
one has been told. The
has been told. The evacuation
been told. The evacuation will
told. The evacuation will not
The evacuation will not come
evacuation will not come for
will not come for thirty-six
not come for thirty-six hours.
come for thirty-six hours.
for thirty-six hours.