From the roof
From the roof you
From the roof you can
the roof you can see
roof you can see directly
you can see directly into
can see directly into the
see directly into the reactor.
directly into the reactor. The
into the reactor. The core
the reactor. The core is
reactor. The core is burning
The core is burning at
core is burning at two
is burning at two thousand
burning at two thousand degrees.
at two thousand degrees. The
two thousand degrees. The air
thousand degrees. The air tastes
degrees. The air tastes like
The air tastes like metal.
air tastes like metal. Your
tastes like metal. Your skin
like metal. Your skin is
metal. Your skin is already
Your skin is already turning
skin is already turning red.
is already turning red. You
already turning red. You have
turning red. You have minutes
red. You have minutes before
You have minutes before the
have minutes before the vomiting
minutes before the vomiting starts.
before the vomiting starts.
the vomiting starts.