They build a
They build a sarcophagus.
They build a sarcophagus. Concrete
build a sarcophagus. Concrete and
a sarcophagus. Concrete and steel.
sarcophagus. Concrete and steel. They
Concrete and steel. They say
and steel. They say it
steel. They say it will
They say it will last
say it will last thirty
it will last thirty years.
will last thirty years. It
last thirty years. It lasted
thirty years. It lasted twenty-nine.
years. It lasted twenty-nine. The
It lasted twenty-nine. The thing
lasted twenty-nine. The thing inside
twenty-nine. The thing inside will
The thing inside will be
thing inside will be dangerous
inside will be dangerous for
will be dangerous for twenty
be dangerous for twenty thousand.
dangerous for twenty thousand.
for twenty thousand.