You press the
You press the emergency
You press the emergency button.
press the emergency button. AZ-5.
the emergency button. AZ-5. The
emergency button. AZ-5. The one
button. AZ-5. The one that
AZ-5. The one that is
The one that is supposed
one that is supposed to
that is supposed to shut
is supposed to shut everything
supposed to shut everything down.
to shut everything down. The
shut everything down. The control
everything down. The control rods
down. The control rods jam.
The control rods jam. The
control rods jam. The power
rods jam. The power does
jam. The power does not
The power does not drop.
power does not drop. It
does not drop. It spikes.
not drop. It spikes. Thirty
drop. It spikes. Thirty thousand
It spikes. Thirty thousand megawatts.
spikes. Thirty thousand megawatts. One
Thirty thousand megawatts. One hundred
thousand megawatts. One hundred times
megawatts. One hundred times what
One hundred times what this
hundred times what this reactor
times what this reactor was
what this reactor was built
this reactor was built for.
reactor was built for.
was built for.