A supervisor arrives.
A supervisor arrives. He
A supervisor arrives. He says
supervisor arrives. He says the
arrives. He says the reactor
He says the reactor is
says the reactor is intact.
the reactor is intact. The
reactor is intact. The dosimeter
is intact. The dosimeter reads
intact. The dosimeter reads three
The dosimeter reads three point
dosimeter reads three point six
reads three point six roentgen.
three point six roentgen. Not
point six roentgen. Not great,
six roentgen. Not great, not
roentgen. Not great, not terrible.
Not great, not terrible. But
great, not terrible. But the
not terrible. But the dosimeter
terrible. But the dosimeter only
But the dosimeter only goes
the dosimeter only goes to
dosimeter only goes to three
only goes to three point
goes to three point six.
to three point six. The
three point six. The actual
point six. The actual level
six. The actual level is
The actual level is fifteen
actual level is fifteen thousand.
level is fifteen thousand.
is fifteen thousand.