Two explosions. The
Two explosions. The thousand-ton
Two explosions. The thousand-ton reactor
explosions. The thousand-ton reactor lid
The thousand-ton reactor lid launches
thousand-ton reactor lid launches into
reactor lid launches into the
lid launches into the air
launches into the air like
into the air like a
the air like a coin.
air like a coin. The
like a coin. The building
a coin. The building tears
coin. The building tears open
The building tears open above
building tears open above you.
tears open above you. You
open above you. You are
above you. You are on
you. You are on the
You are on the floor.
are on the floor. You
on the floor. You cannot
the floor. You cannot hear
floor. You cannot hear anything.
You cannot hear anything.
cannot hear anything.