Six hundred thousand
Six hundred thousand men.
Six hundred thousand men. They
hundred thousand men. They call
thousand men. They call them
men. They call them liquidators.
They call them liquidators. Sent
call them liquidators. Sent to
them liquidators. Sent to clean
liquidators. Sent to clean a
Sent to clean a disaster
to clean a disaster that
clean a disaster that cannot
a disaster that cannot be
disaster that cannot be cleaned.
that cannot be cleaned. The
cannot be cleaned. The robots
be cleaned. The robots they
cleaned. The robots they send
The robots they send in
robots they send in break
they send in break down
send in break down from
in break down from radiation.
break down from radiation. So
down from radiation. So they
from radiation. So they send
radiation. So they send men
So they send men instead.
they send men instead. The
send men instead. The men
men instead. The men call
instead. The men call themselves
The men call themselves bio-robots.
men call themselves bio-robots.
call themselves bio-robots.