You are standing
You are standing at
You are standing at the
are standing at the controls
standing at the controls of
at the controls of an
the controls of an RBMK
controls of an RBMK reactor.
of an RBMK reactor. You
an RBMK reactor. You are
RBMK reactor. You are running
reactor. You are running a
You are running a safety
are running a safety test.
running a safety test. The
a safety test. The power
safety test. The power has
test. The power has dropped
The power has dropped to
power has dropped to two
has dropped to two hundred
dropped to two hundred megawatts.
to two hundred megawatts. Someone
two hundred megawatts. Someone behind
hundred megawatts. Someone behind you
megawatts. Someone behind you says
Someone behind you says keep
behind you says keep going.
you says keep going.
says keep going.