You stagger outside.
You stagger outside. The
You stagger outside. The reactor
stagger outside. The reactor core
outside. The reactor core is
The reactor core is open.
reactor core is open. It
core is open. It is
is open. It is glowing
open. It is glowing blue.
It is glowing blue. There
is glowing blue. There are
glowing blue. There are graphite
blue. There are graphite blocks
There are graphite blocks on
are graphite blocks on the
graphite blocks on the ground.
blocks on the ground. You
on the ground. You pick
the ground. You pick one
ground. You pick one up.
You pick one up. It
pick one up. It burns
one up. It burns your
up. It burns your hand.
It burns your hand. You
burns your hand. You do
your hand. You do not
hand. You do not know
You do not know it
do not know it yet.
not know it yet. But
know it yet. But you
it yet. But you have
yet. But you have just
But you have just received
you have just received a
have just received a lethal
just received a lethal dose
received a lethal dose of
a lethal dose of radiation.
lethal dose of radiation.
dose of radiation.