They send you
They send you to
They send you to the
send you to the roof.
you to the roof. Clear
to the roof. Clear the
the roof. Clear the graphite.
roof. Clear the graphite. You
Clear the graphite. You get
the graphite. You get ninety
graphite. You get ninety seconds.
You get ninety seconds. The
get ninety seconds. The radiation
ninety seconds. The radiation up
seconds. The radiation up here
The radiation up here is
radiation up here is twelve
up here is twelve thousand
here is twelve thousand roentgen
is twelve thousand roentgen per
twelve thousand roentgen per hour.
thousand roentgen per hour. A
roentgen per hour. A lethal
per hour. A lethal dose
hour. A lethal dose takes
A lethal dose takes forty-five
lethal dose takes forty-five seconds.
dose takes forty-five seconds. You
takes forty-five seconds. You are
forty-five seconds. You are on
seconds. You are on the
You are on the roof
are on the roof for
on the roof for ninety.
the roof for ninety.
roof for ninety.