The helicopters come.
The helicopters come. They
The helicopters come. They drop
helicopters come. They drop sand
come. They drop sand and
They drop sand and boron
drop sand and boron into
sand and boron into the
and boron into the open
boron into the open core.
into the open core. The
the open core. The pilots
open core. The pilots fly
core. The pilots fly directly
The pilots fly directly through
pilots fly directly through the
fly directly through the plume.
directly through the plume. They
through the plume. They will
the plume. They will be
plume. They will be dead
They will be dead within
will be dead within weeks.
be dead within weeks. The
dead within weeks. The sand
within weeks. The sand does
weeks. The sand does almost
The sand does almost nothing.
sand does almost nothing.
does almost nothing.