The forest has
The forest has grown
The forest has grown back.
forest has grown back. The
has grown back. The wolves
grown back. The wolves have
back. The wolves have returned.
The wolves have returned. The
wolves have returned. The radiation
have returned. The radiation will
returned. The radiation will outlast
The radiation will outlast everything
radiation will outlast everything you
will outlast everything you have
outlast everything you have ever
everything you have ever known.
you have ever known. You
have ever known. You will
ever known. You will not
known. You will not be
You will not be remembered
will not be remembered for
not be remembered for even
be remembered for even one
remembered for even one of
for even one of those
even one of those twenty
one of those twenty thousand
of those twenty thousand years.
those twenty thousand years.
twenty thousand years.